// content/A1PracticeSlides.js
export const A1_PRACTICE_SLIDES = [
  {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... Alto',
    options: ['basso', 'chiaro', 'grasso', 'insipido', 'pesante'],
    correctAnswer: 0, 
  },
    {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... Saporito',
    options: ['cotto', 'chiaro', 'dolce', 'insipido', 'pesante'],
    correctAnswer: 3, 
  },
    {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... Amaro',
    options: ['basso', 'chiaro', 'dolce', 'insipido', 'dietetico'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
    {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... leggero',
    options: ['basso', 'chiaro', 'cotto', 'dietetico', 'pesante'],
    correctAnswer: 4, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... crudo',
    options: ['basso', 'chiaro', 'cotto', 'insipido', 'pesante'],
    correctAnswer: 2, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... magro',
    options: ['pesante', 'grasso', 'cotto', 'insipido', 'grasso'],
    correctAnswer: 1, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... scuro',
    options: ['basso', 'chiaro', 'cotto', 'insipido', 'dietetico'],
    correctAnswer: 1, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Adjectives',
    question: 'Adjectives and their opposites\n\nMatch the adjectives and their opposites:\n\n... calorico',
    options: ['basso', 'chiaro', 'cotto', 'dietetico', 'pesante'],
    correctAnswer: 4, 
  },




    //Articles1
    {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\n...  mio cantante preferito è Vasco Rossi.',
    options: ['Un', 'Lo', 'Il', 'un'],
    correctAnswer: 2, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\n... suoi genitori si chiamano Enzo e Maria.',
    options: ['Le', 'I', 'La', `un'`],
    correctAnswer: 1, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nVoglio  . . .  automobile nuova.',
    options: ['un', `un'`, 'la', 'il'],
    correctAnswer: 2, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nLuigi ha . . .  amico peruviano.',
    options: ['un', 'uno', `un'`, 'una'],
    correctAnswer: 0, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\n...   mia migliore amica è inglese.',
    options: ['La', 'Una', `Un'`, 'Il'],
    correctAnswer: 0, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nMio fratello ha . . .  influenza.',
    options: ['la', 'una', `l'`, 'un'],
    correctAnswer: 2, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nLoro hanno . . .  figli molto intelligenti.',
    options: ['uno', 'la', 'gli', 'dei'],
    correctAnswer: 3, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nTu ami . . .  alberi e i fiori.',
    options: ['i', 'gli', 'dei', 'una'],
    correctAnswer: 1, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nVoi siete . . .  ragazze molto interessanti.',
    options: ['una', 'le', 'i', 'delle'],
    correctAnswer: 3, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\n...   degli studenti non è italiano.',
    options: ['Uno', 'Lo', 'Un', `Un'`],
    correctAnswer: 0, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nHanno appena costruito . . .  stadio nuovo.',
    options: ['un', 'la', 'uno', 'una'],
    correctAnswer: 3, 
  },
      {
    id: 'Articles1',
    question: 'Choose the correct article.\n\nHo mangiato . . .  lasagne.',
    options: ['la', 'le', 'degli', 'della'],
    correctAnswer: 1, 
  },


  // ... بقیه سؤال‌های همین تمرین با id: 'Adjectives'
  // { id: 'Adjectives', question: '...', options: [...], correctAnswer: ... }
];
